9/26/23, 12:26 AM Resume

MIA CONTRERAS

STUDENT/INTERN

A full-time student majoring in Information Technology. Highly driven and loves to meet others. Efficient and hardworking when needed to meet the priorities of others. Experienced with organizing and leading educational activities. Devoted to promoting a positive experience!

Download Resume

EXPERTISE

- Forensic tool kit (FTK)
- Excel
- HTML CSS
- Python
- Java

REFERENCE

Elgin Kim

Chief Business Officer of Sagaverse

Jun Mai

Manager at Gung ho

EDUCATION

2018-2021

Highschool Diploma

Bolingbrook Highschool

2021-Current

Bachlor Degree

EXPERIENCE

2023 - present

Saga Verse

Brand Ambassador

An internship I got into over the summer, I give the brand content to use such as gaming videos. The videos are edited and posted to their app. I work closely with the app developers to improve the user experience and bring more positive features to the app.

2023 - present

Gung Ho

Assisstant Manager

I currently work at an asian restuant as an assistant manager. It is my job to ensure everything runs smoothly during shifts. I've trained many employees across many different positons, such as cashering, making poke bowls and as a barsita.

AWARDS

2021

Lewis University

CERTIFICATION

2023

ACE

A forensic exam I took for my digital forensic course. After being familiar with FTK and its tools I was able to take the test and get a certification.

Resume

Give Something Back Scholarship

A full ride selective scholorship program, I aquired my freshman year of highschool. Dedicated to helping highschoolers give them a chance to go to college without the financial worry. I got the opportunity to get a mentor who has become a huge help in my college life.

2020

NEHS

A Honor society dedicated to those excelling in english. Was able to be apart of the book club and help host events for the group!

INTEREST

J

 \square

Music Books Travel

CONTACT

Bolingbrook, Illinois

+708-537-2740

Mia718a@gmail.com

SOCIALS

/xxpineapplesxx7

<u>ំ</u>្រា /Mia718a